(Raj:)Don't try to change me, dude.
(Raj:)I am what I am.
(Sheldon:)Oh, gentlemen.
(Howard:)Hey. Aren't you going
to introduce us
(Howard:)to your little friend?
(Sheldon:)My apologies.
(Sheldon:)Raj, Howard, I'd like you to meet Dr.
Robert Oppenheimer.
Hello. Hi.
(Sheldon:)Now, if you'll excuse me,
(Sheldon:)the father of the atomic
bomb wants a saucer of milk.
(Howard:)Okay, I get it.
We're worried about Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Hey.
(Leonard:)Oh, no.
(Sheldon:)Robert Oppenheimer was lonely.
(Leonard:)So you decided to get the
whole Manhattan Project?
(Sheldon:)Yes. This is Enrico Fermi, Richard Feynman,
Edward Teller,  Otto Frisch...
(Sheldon:)...Zazzles.
- Zazzles?
I was going to name him Hermann Von Helmholtz
(Sheldon:)but he's so zazzy.